So now that we've created our empty hash table, the next
现在 我们已经创建了空的哈希表 接下来的
steps are to figure out how to do lookups as well
步骤是弄清楚如何做查询和添加
as adds. Both lookups and adds depend on the same first
查询和添加都依赖于同一个第一步
step. We need to find the right bucket, so that's what
我们需要找到正确的桶 (bucket) 所以这就是
we'll do next. So remember the idea for a hash table,
我们接下来要做的事 想想哈希表的思想
so we have a list of buckets, each bucket is a
那么我们有一个桶的列表 每个桶是一个
list of entries, and each entry is a key, and the
条目的列表 每个条目是一个键 (key) 和一个
list of values. So regardless of whether we want to do lookups and
值列表 所以 不管我们是想要做查找还是
added, and find the value associated with the word, or if we
添加 找到与该词相关联的值 或者如果我们
want to do add and add a new value associated with a word.
要添加 并添加一个与单词相关联的新值
The first thing we always have to do is find the right bucket.
我们总是需要做的第一件事就是找到正确的桶
So if you find the right bucket if we're doing a lookup, the
所以 如果你找到正确的桶 如果我们做一个查找时
next thing we're going to do is need to look through all the entries
我们要做的下一件事就是需要遍历桶中所有条目
in that bucket to find if there's one that matches the key word.
来寻找是否有匹配的关键词
If we're doing add, we also need to start by finding the right
如果我们做添加 我们还需要从找到正确的桶开始
bucket. Then we're going to look through and see if that word already exists.
然后我们要遍历 看看这个词是否已经存在
If it doesn't exist, we can add a new word
如果它不存在 我们可以添加一个新词
and we'll have a new entry, with that word and that
我们将有一个新的条目 具有该单词和该值
value. So both of those depend on first being able to
因此 无论哪个操作都依赖于首先能够找到
find the right bucket, so we'll do that once and be
正确的桶 所以我们会这样做一次 然后
able to reuse that code in both lookup and add.
在查找和添加操作中能够重复使用该代码
So our goal is to define a procedure, and we'll call
因此 我们的目标是定义一个过程 我们称之为
it hashtable_get_bucket, and it'll take two inputs. So it'll take a
hashtable_get_bucket 它需要两个输入 所以它会获取一个
hashtable, and a keyword, and it will output the bucket where
哈希表和一个关键字 然后它将一个桶 其中
that keyword could occur. We don't know yet whether
可能包含有该关键字 我们还不知道
that keyword's actually in the table. It might be somewhere
该关键字是否存在表中 它可能在
in that bucket. It might not. But the important
该桶的某处 也可能没有 但最重要的
thing that hashtable_get_bucket should do, is find the bucket. One
事情 hashtable_get_bucket 应该做的 就是找到该桶
function that will be useful for doing that is
有一个有用的函数是
the hash_string procedure that you defined earlier. And hash_string takes
你之前定义的 hash_string 过程 然后 hash_string 需要
two inputs. It takes a string, which is the
两个输入 它需要一个字符串 也就是
keyword, and it took a size, the number of buckets,
关键词 还有一个尺寸 即桶的数量
and it outputs the number which is the index
然后输出那个桶的索引数字
of that bucket. There's a bit of a mismatch
这里有一些不匹配
here that you'll have to think about to define
你必须考虑定义
hashtable_get_bucket. That hash_string, the input is the size, the
hashtable_get_bucket 也就是 hash_string 输入是尺寸
number of buckets, it's a number. The two inputs
桶的数量 这是一个数字
to hashtable_get_bucket are just the hashtable and a keyword.
hashtable_get_bucket 的两个输入 只是 hashtable 和关键词
So you need to also figure out how to
所以你还需要知道如何
get the size of the hashtable to pass into hash_string.
获得哈希表的大小传递到 hash_string
And if you remember the structure of the hashtable, you
如果你记住哈希表的结构
should be able to figure out how to do that.
你应该能够找出如何做到这一点
Remember our hashtable is a list of buckets, so the
记住我们的哈希表是一个桶列表
value that we want to pass in to the hash_string is the
所以我们想要传递给 hash_string 的值是
size of that hashtable, the number of elements in the
该哈希表的大小 桶列表中的元素数量
list of buckets, that is the hash table. So see if
即哈希表 所以看看
you can define hashtable_get_bucket, and as a hint, you can
你是否可以定义 hashtable_get_bucket 作为提示 你可以
do the whole definition with a very small amount of code.
用少量代码完成整个定义
It should only take one line to do this.
它应该只需要一行代码就可以做到